// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which program is used by web clients to view the web pages ?",
    answer: "Web browser",
    options: [
      "Web browser",
      "Protocol",
      "Web server",
      "Search Engine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which tag is used to display text in title bar of a web document ?",
    answer: "Title tags",
    options: [
      "Body tag",
      "Meta tag",
      "Title tags",
      "Comment tag"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The language that instructs the browser on how to display the hypertext, and adds pictures to the document is __",
    answer: "HTML",
    options: [
      "C",
      "COBOL",
      "python",
      "HTML"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "HTML allows us to use ___ levels of headings",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "2",
      "4",
      "6",
      "5"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which character is used after the opening angular bracket to represent the closing tag?",
    answer: "/",
    options: [
      "?",
      "/",
      "-",
      "("
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "____ are ignored by browser.",
    answer: "Comments",
    options: [
      "Title tag",
      "Comments",
      "Body section",
      "Head section"
    ]
  },
 
  
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which term is used to refer to the computers that are used for storing web pages as files?",
    answer: "Web servers",
    options: [
      "Internet",
      "Web clients",
      "Web servers",
      "World Wide Web"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the abbreviation of HTML?",
    answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
    options: [
      "Hyper Tag Markup Language",
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "Hyper Text Main Language",
      "Hyper Tag Main Language"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The full form of CSS is:",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
    options: [
      "Coloring and Style Sheets",
      "Cascading Style Sheets",
      "Color and Style Sheets",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How can we change the background color of an element?",
    answer: "background-color",
    options: [
      "background-color",
      "color",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
];

